appmaker.xyz 2017-03-06

# Privacy Policies - Appmaker.xyz

## Information we collect

We collect information primarily to provide better services to all of our customers. We collect information you provide us on our Sites such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, fax number, company name, credit card payment information and demographics. We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect on our Sites. When you visit our Sites, some information is automatically collected. This may include information such as the Operating System (OS) running on your device, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type, and language, and the website you visited before our Sites. We also collect information about how you use Appmaker.xyz product. We automatically collect information using "cookies" and Web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website and web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Sites or in our emails. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Sites, our marketing activities, and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Sites. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Sites and could remove cookies used for opt-out of tracking, including our Appmaker.xyz opt-out cookie. 

## How we use information we collect

We use the information we collect primarily to provide, maintain, protect and improve our current products and to develop new ones. We use personal information collected through our Sites as described in this Policy or on our Sites. For example, we may use your information to: Improve our services, Sites and how we operate our business; Understand and enhance your experience using our Sites, products and services; Provide and deliver products and services you request; Respond to your comments or questions and for our Solutions team to provide service; Send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages; Communicate with you about promotions, upcoming events and news about products and services offered by Appmaker.xyz and our selected partners; Link or combine it with other information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and Protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized or illegal activity. 

##  Sharing of personal information

### Information You Share

Our privacy policy does not cover any third party services. To learn about those third parties' privacy practices, please visit their policies. 

### Information We Share

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. Personal Information Security Appmaker.xyz takes reasonable steps to help protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. It is your responsibility to protect your usernames and passwords to help prevent anyone from accessing or abusing your accounts and services. You should not use or reuse the same passwords you use with other accounts as your password for our services. 

## Your information choices and changes

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Appmaker.xyz by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your Appmaker.xyz products or our ongoing business relationship. You may also send requests about your contact preferences, changes and deletions to your information including requests to opt-out of sharing your personal information with third parties by emailing support@appmaker.xyz.We will respond within ninety (90) days to any request to delete your information. Individuals who have provided information to Appmaker.xyz's customers must send requests to change or delete such information to the particular Appmaker.xyz customer. 

## Changes to this policy

We may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above. You agree that your continued use of our Services after such changes have been published to our Services will constitute your acceptance of such revised Policy. Contacting Coffye and Dispute Resolution Coffye provides periodic training for its employees involved in the collection and dissemination of Customer Information. In addition, Coffye's internal policies and procedures provide for disciplinary action if our employees fail to follow this Privacy Policy. We periodically self-assess and review these internal policies and procedures to review compliance. 

You can contact Coffye at:   
Email : mail@coffye.com  
Postal mail:Coffye Innovations PVT LTD  
TBI-NITC  
National Institute of Technology , Calicut  
Kozhikode - 673601  
Kerala  
INDIA  

## Questions

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at support@appmaker.xyz
